<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>vision on Dhanya Abhirami</title>
    <link>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/tags/vision/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vision on Dhanya Abhirami</description>
    <image>
      <title>Dhanya Abhirami</title>
      <url>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 11:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/tags/vision/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The importance of education in National Integration</title>
      <link>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/education-national-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/education-national-integration/</guid>
      <description>The beauty of a garden lies in the varieties of flowers it holds. No one would like a garden if it has a single type of flower. It is nature’s dictum that all different things should co-exist together. Similarly, the beauty of our world lies in the diversity of people with their cultures interwoven.
India is multi-cultural multi-lingual country since ages. With its different facets in every turn – be it religion, language, race, castes, it presents a different beautiful picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How &#39;MAKE IN INDIA&#39; can succeed ?</title>
      <link>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/make-in-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/make-in-india/</guid>
      <description>Make In India is an initiative launched by our Government to encourage multi-national, as well as national companies to manufacture their products in India. The objective of this initiative is to transform India into a global design and manufacturing hub.
Our country has 16% of world population. So, in pure technical sense, one in six objects produced anywhere in the world should find its market in India. If we become self-reliant in our requirements, the precious foreign exchange will not go out of our country.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
