<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dhanya Abhirami</title>
    <link>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dhanya Abhirami</description>
    <image>
      <title>Dhanya Abhirami</title>
      <url>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.150.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Joy of Missing Out</title>
      <link>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/jomo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/jomo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Picture this: It’s a breezy Saturday evening. You’re sitting at home in the balcony, quietly reading a book, sipping your coffee. It’s one of those rare peaceful days—just the way you like it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, your phone buzzes. You pick it up and open Instagram.
Someone you know is out clubbing, posting story after story: the music, the dancing, the food. And another friend shares photos from an exotic resort, swimming in a stunning infinity pool.  All happening without you&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Boat – Sailing through Drinks and Memories</title>
      <link>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/paperboat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/paperboat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;synopsis&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This case study describes and analyses the growth of a business that challenged powerful multinational companies.Paper Boat is a beverage company that manufactures authentic Indian traditional juices and drinks. The company used the new age marketing strategies like story-telling to create engaging content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;target-group&#34;&gt;Target Group&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This case provides an overview of an indigenous business and is intended to undergraduate students in pre-final and final year of undergraduate courses. This case also adds value to research community and startup training institutions as an example of a small company that stood against the competitive challenge posed by international giants using its unique marketing strategy.
This case could also be extended to MBA students who can analyse and strategize methodologies for the company to succeed in the market.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The importance of education in National Integration</title>
      <link>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/education-national-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/education-national-integration/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The beauty of a garden lies in the varieties of flowers it holds. No one would like a garden if it has a single type of flower. It is nature’s dictum that all different things should co-exist together. Similarly, the beauty of our world lies in the diversity of people with their cultures interwoven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;India is multi-cultural multi-lingual country since ages. With its different facets in every turn – be it religion, language, race, castes, it presents a different beautiful picture. Diversity is one thing we all have in common. In spite of having such diverse dimensions, one thing we have in common is our affinity to Mother land – India. On Mother India, Mahakavi Subramanya Bharati said, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Ival Seppu Mozhi Pathinettudayaal, enir sinthanai ondrudayal&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;, - which roughly translates as &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Mother India speaks different languages, but her thought is unified and towards a common goal&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;. That was the confidence and superiority complex Bharati had a century ago, when the education levels were in pathetic condition and British controlling almost whole of India. Today, after 7 decades of independence, we are definitely far better. However, to develop and make our country a leader in the world, we need to take all our people together. To nurture and develop the spirit of national integration, education acts as a catalyst.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How &#39;MAKE IN INDIA&#39; can succeed ?</title>
      <link>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/make-in-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dhanya-abhirami.github.io/posts/make-in-india/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Make In India is an initiative launched by our Government to encourage multi-national, as well as national companies to manufacture their products in India. The objective of this initiative is to transform India into a global design and manufacturing hub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our country has 16% of world population. So, in pure technical sense, one in six objects produced anywhere in the world should find its market in India.  If we become self-reliant in our requirements, the precious foreign exchange will not go out of our country. For achieving this, we need to focus on areas like quality, reliability, variety, affordability, which are vital for any product to survive the cut-throat competition posed by mighty giants from abroad. We should achieve international standards in all these aspects. In today’s world, survival holds the key to success.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
